on the spot
yeah
[Music]
yeah I basically got a job at cron where
I could focus on the development part
and Technical part and pretty much have
been doing that for the past 24 25 years
so I started as a financial uh
controller and I was working with
figures but I didn't find that exciting
enough so I wanted to be to get to know
the other side of the of the job and to
to know the system and then I got to
know Business Center and I like the
product so much that I decided to become
a consultant and your financial
knowledge is really helping you to get
business Central very quickly it's
easily to to to know how the settings
are or how you have to do the settings
but it's not easy to know the background
of things so you have to know the
financial knowledge but maybe you you
have a sale job or purchase job and and
you know how to do purchase planning or
you you know how to work in a warehouse
yeah that is knowledge you cannot learn
in a system so the Practical knowledge
you have will really help you to
implement and to make you a successful
consultant first of all we need new
Talent uh because we have a lot of work
right uh the the market is picking up
and we need to do a lot of
implementations and usually the young
people are very let's say related to
that new technology from socials to AI
to whatnot our youngest kids was
downloading AI he's 10 years old so what
will he know about 10 years when he's 18
he will know a lot more than we know
yeah yeah he he asked the right
questions on coil